Come on, we'll take your mom
to see the Hollywood sign...
(Mrs Cooper:)...the Wax Museum,
the Walk of Fame.
(Penny:)Ooh. Maybe a little Rodeo Drive.
Well, I can't spend $12,000
on a handbag...
(Mrs Cooper:)...but it's free to look upon those
who do with righteous condemnation.
- What do you say?
- What do I say?
(Sheldon:)I say you people need to stop ruining
my mom's visit with your sushi...
(Sheldon:)...and your sadness
and your slutty shirts.
(Sheldon:)Stop it.
(Howard(after Raj whispers to him):)He's not talking about your shirt.
Your shirt is fine.
(Leonard:)These are delicious.
(Mrs Cooper:)The trick to pancakes is bacon grease.
I cook everything in it.
(Leonard:)Everything?
Aren't you worried about your heaIth?
(Mrs Cooper:)Doctors are always changing
their mind.
(Mrs Cooper:)One week bacon grease
is bad for you.
(Mrs Cooper:)Next week
we're not getting enough of it.
(Mrs Cooper:)Good morning, Shelly.